legalinsurrection.com 2019-06-16

# Privacy Policy

**INSURRECTION WEBSITES**

**PRIVACY POLICY**

WAJ Media LLC dba Legal Insurrection and College Insurrection, and effective March 1, 2019, the [Legal Insurrection Foundation ](https://legalinsurrectionfoundation.org/) (“Insurrection” or “Company”), considers the privacy of the users of [www.legalinsurrection.com,](http://www.legalinsurrection.com/) [www.collegeinsurrection.com](http://www.collegeinsurrection.com/), and [www.legalinsurrectionfoundation.org](https://legalinsurrectionfoundation.org/)  (the “Website”) to be of utmost importance and works to protect it. Insurrection recognizes that you may be concerned about Insurrection’s collection, use, and disclosure of the personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that is collected when you use the Website and the services offered on the Website (the “Services”). This Privacy Policy describes the information that we collect from you, how we collect this information, and what we do with it after we collect it. By using the Website and the Services you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [contact@legalinsurrection.com](mailto:contact@legalinsurrection.com).

Insurrection collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the Website and the Services. Insurrection also collects other profile data including but not limited to: political influences, gender, age, and occupation in order to assist users in properly utilizing the Services.

Insurrection also logs non-personally-identifiable information including, but not limited to, IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the Website. This data is used to manage the Website, track usage and improve the Website and the Services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

The information provided by each user, including users’ names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction with respect to the Services. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new users to sign-up for the Services and to send notifications related to the Services. With the exception of inviting new users, and sending out notifications, a user’s email address is not shared or displayed to people, unless otherwise expressly agreed to by the user or if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with legal process; (b) enforce Insurrection Terms and Conditions of Use (<https://legalinsurrection.com/terms-and-conditions-of-use/>); (c) respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third parties; or (d) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Insurrection, its users and the public. Users’ full names are never directly revealed to other users of the Services. To facilitate searching and finding a user’s comments on the Website, Insurrection allows users to search for other users using usernames.

We may also use a user’s email address to send updates or news regarding the Website and/or Services.

From time to time, Insurrection or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstakes or contest on the Website. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain advertising partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

**COMMUNICATIONS TO NON-USERS**

Website users can invite family, friends or acquaintances to join the Services by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system, including, but not limited to, using RSS Feeds. Insurrection stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the user’s list of the user sending the invitations. Recipients of invitations from the Website may contact Insurrection to request the removal of their information from our database. You may prevent Insurrection email invitations and other messages from being sent to any email address you control by sending a single email requesting such invitations and messages to be blocked to [contact@legalinsurrection.com](mailto:contact@legalinsurrection.com).  Please note that the email must come from the account you wish to block. ** **

**USE OF COOKIES** ** **

Insurrection uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences and to record session information for purposes including insuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize advertising and Website content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on the Website. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. However, you must enable cookies from Insurrection in order to use most functions on the Website. Please note that Insurrection uses third-party advertising companies to provide advertisments when you visit the Website. These third-party advertisers may be allowed to present advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this Website and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Please note that Google Inc. (“Google”), one of the third-party vendor adverting companies referenced above, uses cookies to provide advertisements on the Website. Google’s use of cookies enables it to provide advertisements to the Company’s users based on their visit to the Insurrection’s sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of Google cookies by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Advertiser use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies and not the Insurrection Privacy Policy.

**LINKS**

This Website may contain links to other sites. Insurrection is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices on these other sites. When linking to another site, a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our Privacy Policy solely governs information collected on the Website. ** **

**MESSAGE BOARDS AND PUBLIC FORUMS** ** **

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to message boards or any other public forums, that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING** ** **

Ads appearing on this Website may be delivered to users by Insurrection or one of our advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow advertisement providers to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, advertisement providers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers solely the use of cookies by Insurrection and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

<http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/>

**SECURITY**

Insurrection user accounts are secured by user-created passwords. Insurrection takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to only those individuals who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time For any additional information about the security measures we use on Insurrection, please contact us at [contact@legalinsurrection.com](mailto:contact@legalinsurrection.com).

**SHARING AND DISCLOSURE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION**

Except as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy, Insurrection does not share your personally identifiable information with other organizations for their marketing to you; however, we may use unaffiliated companies to help us maintain and operate our Website or other reasons to operate our business, and these organizations may receive your personally identifiable information. We may disclose personal information to satisfy government requests, legal requirements, and protect the rights and property of Insurrection, users, and affiliates. Insurrection reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Insurrection or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest.

**CHANGES IN OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

From time to time Insurrection may make changes to its Privacy Policy. Any changes will be posted on the Website to make users aware of which changes have occurred so that users will be aware of the information being collected, how it’s used and when it may be disclosed. Users are bound by any changes to the policy when he or she uses the Website after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use a user’s personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated herein, we will notify you by posting a notice on our Website for at least thirty (30) days in advance of such a change. ** **

**MINORS**

We do not collect or solicit information from, approve applications for, or maintain accounts for any minor we know to be, or have reason to believe is, under the age of 18.

**CHANGES**

If you would like to change, update, or delete your personal information at any time, you may log in using your Username for changes and updates, or send us an email to [contact@legalinsurrection.com](mailto:contact@legalinsurrection.com) to delete.

**COMMUNICATIONS**

We may send you messages and updates about Insurrection, our Services, affiliates, promotions, etc. If you prefer not to receive non-transaction information, please send us an email at [contact@legalinsurrection.com](mailto:contact@legalinsurrection.com).

All contents of the Services and any other service provided hereunder are © Legal Insurrection and College Insurrection and the Legal Insurrection Foundation, respectively, or its licensors. Photographs and illustrations are copyrighted by their respective owners, as noted in the credits.

Copyright © 2012-2019.   All rights reserved.

Effective Date:  August 21, 2012

Last updated:  March 1, 2019
